shopandship.co.za 2010-06-24

# Shop and Ship Online (Pty) Ltd - Privacy Policy

Shop and Ship Online (Pty) Ltd is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy applies to all the web pages related to this website. 

All the information gathered in the online forms on the website is used to personally identify users that subscribe to this service. The information will not be used for anything other that which is stated in the Terms & Conditions of use for this service. None of the information will be sold or made available to any third parties. 

The site may collect certain information about user’s visits, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the site; the pages that you access while at the site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the site, analyze trends, and administer the site. 

Shop and Ship Online (Pty) Ltd may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our site. Shop and Ship Online (Pty) Ltd will post those changes, ensuring users are always aware, regarding, what information Shop and Ship Online (Pty) Ltd gathers, how Shop and Ship Online (Pty) Ltd might use that information, and whether Shop and Ship Online (Pty) Ltd will disclose that information to any parties. Please refer back to this policy regularly. Should there be any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please send Shop and Ship Online (Pty) Ltd an [E-mail.](mailto:info@shopandship.co.za?subject=Terms%20and%20Conditions%20query)

By using this website, users signify their acceptance of Shop and Ship Online (Pty) Ltd’s Terms and Conditions. If users do not agree with this policy, please contact Shop and Ship Online (Pty) Ltd or alternatively refrain from using our site. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to these terms will signify that you accept those changes. 

COOKIE/TRACKING TECHNOLOGY The site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. 

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**

In an attempt to provide increased value to our users, Shop and Ship Online (Pty) Ltd may provide links to other websites or resources. Users acknowledge and agree that Shop and Ship Online (Pty) Ltd is not responsible for the availability of such external sites or resources, do not endorse, and are not responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for the privacy practices or the content (including misrepresentative or defamatory content) of such websites, including (without limitation) any advertising, products or other materials or services on or available from such websites or resources, nor for any damage, loss or offence caused or alleged to be caused by, or in connection with, the use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on such external sites or resources.
